http://www.rasc.ca/privacy

Online Activities | Dorner Telescope Museum
Log inTo access members' resources please login below using your RASC ID and password (help):
Username *
Password *
Join Now
Renew Membership
DonateSocietyMission StatementAbout UsAnnual ReportsAwardsBoard of DirectorsCommitteesMembers of NoteCentresDonationsGeneral AssemblyRASC SponsorsPublicationsObserver's HandbookObserver's CalendarJournalSkywaysThe BulletinObservingObserving ProgramsTips & ExpectationsAstroimaging CertificateProjectsStar PartiesAstroSketchersProgramsAstronomy in CanadaCanadian AsteroidsCanadian CometsCanadian MeteoritesObservatoriesScience Museums and PlanetariaNetwork ComputingEducation / OutreachRecent VideosAstronomy EventsClassroom HelpCurriculum AidsLesson PlansDiscover the UniverseProfessional DevelopmentScience Fair ProjectsHomework HelpWebsites and AppsExtra ResourcesRASC ResourcesAstro PodcastsWolf Cub Badge RequirementsGirl Guide Badge RequirementsLight-Pollution AbatementHistoryNational ArchivesDorner Telescope MuseumOur Printed HistoryLogbooksEncyclopedia UranicaPast General AssembliesSpecial Projects ProgramPublic Lectures / SpeakersMember AreaVolunteerContact UsMember ServiceAsk An AstronomereStore
Search form
Search
You are hereHome
Privacy Policy
Created by Bonnie Bird, Peter Jedicke, and Kim Hay.
Approved by National Council 2004-03-06
Motion 04118
Reference: RASC Policy Manual: Policy G18: Privacy Policy (Preamble)
General Statement
Effective 2004 January 1, The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada is required to comply with federal legislation governing the use, collection, and disclosure of personal information in the course of our commercial activities. We have implemented a corporate Privacy Policy in order to do so. Our Privacy Policy addresses the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information. Personal information is information about an identifiable individual and does not include information about corporations, partnerships, or other non-individuals. The personal information the RASC collects will depend on the service we provide to you.
The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of our members' and customers' personal information.
The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada is following the Canadian Standards Association's Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information (CAN/CSA-Q830-96).
The Key articles of the Acts provisions are:
organizations are required to seek the consent of individuals prior to collecting, using, or disclosing their personal information; organizations must protect personal information with security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information; and
individuals may access personal information about themselves held by an organization and have it corrected, if necessary.
exemptions include journalistic, artistic, or literary purposes.
We may collect, use, and disclose personal information to respond to application for membership, to provide our services to you, and/or to further the aims of The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, which include the promotion and advancement of astronomy and allied sciences.
The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada ("RASC") is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your personal information. As part of this commitment, the following Ten Privacy Principles govern our actions as they relate to the use of customer information. The principles have been built upon the values set by the Canadian Standards Association's Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information and Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.
Author: AnonymousPost date: Thursday, June 3, 2010 - 11:55amLast modified: Saturday, February 1, 2020 - 12:12pm
© Copyright 2020 The Royal Astronomical Society of Canada. All rights reserved.
